STEFAN BOBROWSKI

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

203-395-2674

□ stefanbobrowski1@gmail.com

P Shelton, CT

https://stefanbobrowski.com

https://www.linkedin.com/in/stefanbobrowski/

https://github.com/stefanbobrowski

https://stackoverflow.com/users/3317728/stefanbob

SUMMARY

Software Engineer, Web Developer. and Game Developer with over 10 years of experience. Passionate about creating exceptional applications that help people, writing clean & performant code, and learning the latest technology. Aspires to push the boundaries of user-experience and content creation.

SKILLS

JavaScript, React, Git, Github, Node, Express, MongoDB, SCSS, Unreal Engine 5, Photoshop

EXPERIENCE

Home Depot - *Remote* - Software Engineer *May 2021 - present*

Vibrant Software - Remote - Software Developer July 2020 - January 2021

Hat Trick Designs LLC - *New York, NY* - Full Stack Web Developer *June 2019 - July 2020*

Direct Wines - *Norwalk, CT* - Front-End Web Developer *February 2019 - May 2019*

Kathy Kuo Home - *New York, NY* - Front-End Web Developer *January 2018 - September 2018*

Archi FX LLC - *Remote* - Web Developer *August 2017 - January 2018*

Healthcasts - *New York, NY* - Front-End Web Developer *December 2016 - July 2017*

Finalsite - *Glastonbury, CT* - Front-End Web Developer *September 2014 - November 2016*

EDUCATION

University of Connecticut - Bachelor of Science in Computer Science 2010 -2014